It's as real as the feelings you feel.
The Princess Bride is a adventure, family, fantasy film directed by Rob Reiner.
In this enchantingly cracked fairy tale, the beautiful Princess Buttercup and the dashing Westley must overcome staggering
odds to find happiness amid six-fingered swordsmen, murderous princes, Sicilians and rodents of unusual size.
But even death can't stop these true lovebirds from triumphing.
Westley, played by Cary Elwes.
The Princess Bride, played by Robin Wright.
Inigo Montoya, played by Mandy Patinkin.
Prince Humperdinck, played by Chris Sarandon.
Count Rugen, played by Christopher Guest.
Vizzini, played by Wallace Shawn.
The Princess Bride may refer to:
The Princess Bride (novel), 1973 fantasy romance novel by writer William Goldman
The Princess Bride (film), 1987 American film adaptation directed by Rob Reiner
The Princess
Bride (soundtrack), a 1987 soundtrack for the film
Home Movie: The Princess Bride, a 2020 tribute performance of the film
Princess Bride (Japanese: プリンセスブライド), a dating sim released in 2003.
Princess Bride!, theme song by Kotoko (musician).
The film explores themes of dreams, based on novel or
book, narration, wrestling, miracle.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.